Previously on
Two and a Half Men...
I think
we can all agree
that Charlie lived life
to its fullest
and-and gave it
everything he had.
Gave me herpes.
I still don't see
why we have to sell.
I mean, he left it to me.
Obviously, he wanted me
to have it.
Can you make
the mortgage payments?
Not per say.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I was just trying
to drown myself.
You tried to
commit suicide?
Yeah.
I had no idea that the water
would be that cold.
I have been
where you are.
Uh, rejected,
friendless, broke.
I'm not broke.
I'm worth, like,
a billion dollars.
Beg pardon?
I just went to one funeral,
I don't want to be
involved in another one.
Why don't you and I go out
and have a drink and talk?
About what?
Why somebody would want
to kill themselves when they
have a billion freakin' dollars.
My...
wife dumped me,
and I want to die.
I don't know
if I can ever love anyone
the way that I love her.
Oh, it'll be okay.
Oh, God,
I miss my wife!
Guess what.
I had sex
with two girls last night.
Great. Um, I masturbated
and cried myself to sleep.
I like my night better.
Hey, I dig your house,
so I'm gonna buy it, okay?
O-Okay.
You're the best.
Oh. Ugh.
Whoa.
Um, this is Walden.
He's gonna buy
the house.
Welcome to
my humble abode.
♪ Men. ♪
So, what do think?
Will you stay on?
I'd consider it,
if the price is right.
I'd also consider
smothering you
with my sweet, sweet loving.
Well, money is not an issue.
Good to know.
Ka-ching.
What's down here?
Ice.
Mm. I like it better on top.
Me, too, puppy.
Anyway, what I
really need is
a housekeeper who's gonna
be here all the time.
'Cause, you know, I'm not very
good at king care of myself.
Oh, I can take care of you.
Oh, I can
take care of you.
Well, my car's all packed.
I guess I'm ready to go.
Great news, Alan.
Berta has agreed to be
my live-in housekeeper.
Really?
Yeah, he talked me into it.
I wonder what his sweat
tastes like.
Well, that is good news.
Uh, here are
a couple of sets of keys,
remotes for the garage,
and remember,
garbage pickup is on Tuesday.
Oh, you take care
of the garbage, right?
Nope.
Well, uh, guess it's time
for me to go.
Wait. Come here.
Give us a hug good-bye.
Seriously?
Come on, Alan.
Despite everything, you and me
have been like family.
Uh, I guess.
I'm taking
your room, Zippy.
Of course you are.
Well, see ya.
I'll walk you out.
I could bite that ass
like an apple.
Well, I hope you'll be
very happy here, Walden.
Thank you. I don't
know if I can be
happy anywhere
without my wife.
Oh, come on,
you're young, you're rich,
and you've got a face
that gives women an erection.
What about love?
What about commitment?
What about spending a lifetime
with your spiritual soul mate?
Hey, look, a peephole!
Hello!
Man, I love peepholes.
Well, you know what they say.
People who love peepholes...
are the luckiest people
in the world.
Okay, good luck.
Hey, thank you
for all your help and advice.
Oh, you're welcome.
Uh, and if you ever need
a friend to talk to man-to-man,
you know where to find me.
Your mommy's.
Only temporarily.
Okay.
Well, uh, if I left
anything here,
feel free to, you know, keep it,
throw it away, whatever.
Great. Bye.
Bye.
Bye!
Okay, Walden Schmidt.
It is time to start your new
life as a single man in Malibu.
Hello?
Dad?
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah. ♪
♪ Men. ♪
♪ Two and a Half Men 9x02 ♪
People Who Love Peepholes
Original Air Date on September 26, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
♪ Men. ♪
Why are you
unpacking?
Because you told me
I could stay here.
Temporarily.
Yeah, a few days,
a couple of weeks,
a month, tops.
Yeah, right.
Why can't you just stay
with your girlfriend?
Oh, oh, this isn't a very good
time for Lyndsey and I
to be moving in together.
Why not?
Well, she's going through
one of those phases where,
uh, the very touch of me
fills her with revulsion.
Um...
I-I'm thinking
it's premenopause.
Yes, I'm sure that's why.
Well, just so you know,
I'm not putting my life on hold
while you're here.
Oh, and I wouldn't
expect you to.
Just go on with your life.
Do whatever it is you would do,
as if I weren't here.
Well, I have a date tonight.
Oh, great.
We'll probably
wind up having sex.
Sure.
Rough sex.
Right.
So, stay away from my bedroom.
No problem.
Even if you hear me screaming.
Especially if I hear you
screaming.
Unless I'm repeatedly
screaming "umbrella."
U-Umbrella?
That's my safe word.
Sometimes they can't hear it
through the leather mask.
Most moms would've stopped with
"I have a date tonight."
♪ Men. ♪
Hey, Bridge, it's me again.
What is the name of
that shampoo that I use
that doesn't sting my eyes?
Baby shampoo?
Where do I get it?
Any supermarket.
That is remarkably convenient.
Oh, uh, while I have you
on the phone,
will you take me back?
Wow, it's like "no"
is your favorite word now.
Okay, whoa, don't hang up,
don't hang up.
Hey, uh, what is
the toilet paper that we use?
You know, the stuff that's
soft on my tushy like a cloud.
You grow up.
H-Hello?
Hey, Berta, will you
run to the supermarket
and get me baby shampoo?
Sure.
Then I'll sit in the tub
with you and wash your hair.
Oh, Berta.
I miss her so much.
Oh, hey.
Hey, everything's
gonna be all right.
Just wait and see.
I've never felt
so bad in my life.
And I never felt so good.
Don't!
Stop!
What are you doing?
I said don't stop!
I should be on the roof
with a rifle.
- Oh. Hey, Walden.
- Hey.
Uh, you left some books
in your room.
Oh, thank you.
Um, you didn't have to
drive all the way over here.
Is it really possible
to hypnotize a woman
and make her your slave?
Oh.
That was a, that was a
gag gift for my birthday.
What about Ten Minutes a Day
to Incredible Wealth?
Oh, good, that's
my poop book.
Um, I'd invite you in,
but my mom doesn't let
me have friends over.
That's cool.
Mm.
You want to go out
and maybe do something?
What do you
have in mind?
Umbrella!
Doesn't matter,
let's go.
Umbrella!
Umbrella! Umbr...
Nice car.
What is it?
It's an
electric Fisker.
State-of-the-art
lithium ion technology
supplemented with a
turbo-charged engine.
Solar panels
on the roof.
Oh, blue Volkswagen.
Punchbug!
So, how much does
something like this cost?
About a hundred grand.
It's great for the environment.
I don't know why anyone
would drive anything else.
Speaking for myself,
bone-crushing poverty
is something of
a stumbling block.
Maybe you could lease.
I got a confession
to make, Alan.
Me, too.
The hypnotism book
wasn't really a gift.
I really came over because...
I was kind of lonely.
Oh, sure, sure.
I been there.
A lot.
In fact, I'm there now.
I've never really spent
much time alone.
I've been with Bridget
since high school.
Mm. High school sweethearts.
When I was in high school,
I was dating a poster
of Molly Ringwald.
You know, back then,
she was crazy in love with me.
I didn't even have
any money then.
Oh, I'm sure
she still loves you.
No.
She's changed.
Her heart has become
cold and angry.
Um, you're starting to go
a little fast there, buddy.
I mean, who just wakes up
one day and all of a sudden
decides they don't want
to be married anymore?
Uh, well, actually,
it only seems that way.
In my experience,
they've been mulling it over
for quite a while.
Uh, you know, the speed limit
is 35, and you're going,
oh, oh, 80.
I mean, what ever happened
to till death do us part?
Yeah, who died?
Not you, not her.
Oh, good golly, 95.
Whoa! Whoa!
This thing really
takes the corners.
I love her, Alan,
and I want her back.
Well, I know you do.
Oh, 103, Walden, 103.
Life is not worth
living without Bridget!
Truck, truck, truck!
It hurts so much, I
can't take it anymore!
Umbrella!
♪ Men. ♪
I'm sorry I scared you
by driving so fast.
That's okay.
I'm sorry I peed a little
on your seat.
Where are we?
We're going
to my house.
I got to talk Bridget
into taking me back.
Oh, no.
No, no, bad idea.
When a woman says she doesn't
want you, begging does not help.
And I say this having spent
more time on my knees
than any straight man
in America.
What is this,
a gated community?
No, it's just
my house.
Wow.
Instead of going
to chiropractor school,
I should have
married a billionaire.
Next time,
you'll know.
What are you doing here, Walden?
I just want to talk to you.
Go away or I'll call the police!
"Go away
or I'll call the police."
Man, that takes me back.
Um, what do you say
I drive us home?
How about that?
I'm not giving up that easy.
Oh, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa!
W-Where...?
You heard what she said
about the police, right?
I'm going to get my wife back.
Come on.
Come on?
What's my part in this?
I need you to help me
over the gate.
O-Okay.
Again, voice of experience here.
Criminal trespass usually ends
with her dating the cop.
Will you just come on.
Here, give me a hand.
Here, let me go.
I'm going this way.
I got it.
Okay, okay.
Good luck.
Come on.
Again, come on?
I may need your help
getting in a window.
Oh, terrific.
Now I'm Spider-Man.
I got you.
Walden, do not make me
turn that gate on.
W-What does that mean?
Turn the gate on?
Don't worry, she's bluffing.
I still have
a buzzing in my ears.
I can't hear you, I have
God, Walden, what
is wrong with you?
Well, if loving you
is wrong, then...
I am wrong.
It's true.
He talks about you all the time.
Okay, I expect
this kind of thing from him;
he has the emotional maturity
of a 12-year-old.
What's your excuse?
Uh, I live at my mom's,
and she's having
rough sex with a stranger, and
I had to get out of the house.
Honey, I just don't understand
why we can't work things out.
Okay, I'll tell you again.
Oh, this part
is never good.
I'm tired of living
with a child.
I'm tired of being
more of a mother than a wife.
Whoa, oh,
whoa, whoa.
You are not more of
a mother than a wife.
Really? Who picks out
your clothes?
You.
Who tells you
when to go to sleep?
You.
Who does all the cooking
and cleaning around here?
The cooking and the
cleaning ladies.
Before we were rich!
You.
Look, Walden, you're a sweet guy
and I'll always love you,
but I can't live
with Peter Pan anymore.
Uh, now, now,
to be fair,
uh, Peter Pan
didn't want to grow up.
Uh, from what I understand,
Walden's just never had to.
Sorry.
Seemed important
up here.
Down here,
not so much.
Bridget, believe
me, I can grow up.
Oh, please.
At least give me
a chance to try.
I gave you 15 years.
It's over!
Okay.
Can I at least play
a little Donkey Kong
with Alan before I go?
Are you insane?!
Get out!
Oh, yeah, fine,
I'm insane!
Come on, Alan!
Thank you for the water
and the...
Hold on.
Let's go.
Where does she get off
calling me a child?
Um, you seem a little upset;
maybe I should drive us. Um...
She is a stupid-head.
Oh, oh, white Volkswagen.
Huh?
Huh? Come on.
Oh, wait, wait,
I've got an idea.
Why don't we stop,
have a drink and talk about it.
Drinking is not the answer.
No, stopping is the answer!
Oh, dear God,
where is that toilet paper?!
Oh, boy.
Alan?
Yeah?
Why are you
lying on top of me?
'Cause I didn't want
to be on the bottom?
I think we're naked.
Yeah. You can ignore
what's going on down there.
That was a
morning reflex.
Could you get it
off of me, please?
Absolutely.
Do you remember anything?
Uh...
we went to a liquor store,
and then we came back here.
Then we went
skinny dipping.
Right, right.
Whose idea was that?
Mine.
Shh.
♪ Men. ♪
Okay, your pants
are clean.
Thank you.
adult diapers.
Look, Walden was driving
ridiculously fast,
and-and I have
a nervous bladder.
Save it, Zippy.
This is not my first
pee stain rodeo with you.
Hi. Is Charlie here?
Oh, God, another one.
You deal with it.
Um, hi.
I'm-I'm Charlie's brother Alan.
I'm Penelope.
Is he here?
Uh, maybe you better sit down.
Is-Is everything okay?
Um, no.
Penelope, the-the thing is,
uh, Charlie passed away.
What?
It was very sudden.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry, he was just
such a terrific guy.
I can't believe he's gone.
Hey, what's going on?
Hello, I'm Penelope.
Hi. I'm Walden.
What are you crying about?
I have no idea.
Don't worry about me,
I'll let myself out.
You smell good.
Oh, thank you.
It's baby shampoo.
"What are you crying about?"
"I have no idea."
Oh, Bridget. Hi.
Hi.
I came to talk to Walden.
Really?
Yeah, I think maybe
I've been a little
hard on him.
Well, um...
Bridget?
Hey.
Walden?
Look who came
to talk to you, Walden.
Your wife.
You're married?
Oh, yeah, long time married.
Uh, they just met.
This is Penelope, my girlfriend.
What?
Shut up and walk.
I'm-I'm glad you came.
Come, sit-sit down.
When I saw you with that girl,
I thought that maybe
she was with you.
You're kidding, right?
I mean, come on,
Alan's the ladies' man.
He's a total
pickup artist.
Come on!
Charlie's dead,
Walden's married,
what's wrong
with me?!
♪ Men. ♪
So, I was thinking
we could go out to
dinner sometime.
Let me prove that
I can change.
I can be a grown-up.
I guess I owe you
that much.
Sweet!
Sorry to interrupt.
I was just on a little jog
with my lady.
Uh, I'll, uh,
get out of your way.
Uh, hold on.
I'm-I'm going to say
good-bye to my guest,
because that's the grown-up
thing to do, right?
Alan, thank you.
You saved my
butt back there.
Oh, I'm glad
things are working out.
I owe you big-time.
If there's anything
that you need,
any way I can help you,
you just let me know.
Well, since you mention it,
you could do me a little favor.
Name it.
Well, really uncomfortable
living at my mom's.
Um, do you think I could
stay here for a few days
till I find my own place?
No problem.
Few days, couple weeks.
Yeah, done.
Month, tops.
Whatever.
Great, great. Thanks.
And, uh, and don't worry,
I'm not one
to overstay my welcome.
Cool.
I'm back.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==